Guide to the Teacher Preparation and Placement Program, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Teacher Preparation and Placement Program, Yale College, records
1953-2007
RU 179
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
96
2.58
The records consist of administrative and student files documenting the Yale Teacher Preparation and Placement Program.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-E (YRG 9-E), Records documenting Yale College offices, programs, and projects.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative and student files documenting the Yale Teacher Preparation and Placement Program.
College placement services; Teachers -- Selection and appointment; Teachers -- Training of; Teaching; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Students
- Records, 1953-1976; Accession 1973-A-005
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Administrative files, 1949-1972
    - Agencies: commercial teaching, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alumni placement service, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual report, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Career advisory office, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cobham Hall: England, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Commencement programs, 1959-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
    - Correspondence, general, 1960-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - Indian Affairs, Bureau of, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Independent Schools, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - National Education Association (NEA) computerized placement, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - National teacher examinations: forms and information (including test scores), 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - New England Association for School, College and University staffing, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Overseas School of London, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Positions, general, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Promotion, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Public school vacancies
      - Registrants
        - New, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Prospective, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    - Requisitions: placement, materials, supplies, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
    - State Employment Service, Connecticut, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Yale Daily News, correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Yale men in teaching: lists, 1949-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - Awards, 1956-1970
    - Secondary School Teachers, Outstanding
      - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - 1963 (Box 4, Folder 2-5)
      - 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
      - 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
      - 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
      - 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
      - 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
      - 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
      - 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Secondary School Teacher Preparation Program: general information, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Secondary School Teacher Program: meetings, 1956-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - Conferences, 1955-1970
    - English
      - 1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - 1959 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - 1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - 1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - 1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - 1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - English and social studies: clerical, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Social studies
      - 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - 1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - 1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - 1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - 1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - 1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - Fifteenth conference
        - Arrangements, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence and invitations, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, general: after-conference, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
        - Teaching about Asia at Secondary Level: copyright, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Teaching about Asia at Secondary Level: publicity and orders, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Master of Arts in Teaching (MAT), 1951-1971
    - Advisory Board, public schools, role of Connecticut study, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Annual lists, 1951-1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut certification, 1955-1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut State Board of Education, 1954-1959 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Course files
      - English-history (summer), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1955-1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Numbers, course, 1951-1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Smith-Vassar-Yale plan: correspondence and credit, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - #52: Student project, 1955-1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - #100: Secondary schools, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - #101: Practice teaching, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
      - #104: History and philosophy of education, 1954-1969 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
      - #104b-105: History and philosophy of education, 1956-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - #106, 130b: Educational psychology, 1964-1970 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
      - #108: Child growth and development, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - #130: English, methods of teaching, 1964-1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - #130a: History, methods and teaching, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - #131b: Latin, methods of teaching, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - #140: Social sciences teaching, 1955-1959 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - #140s: English novel studies, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - #150: Science teaching, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - #160: Modern languages teaching, 1956-1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - #173s: Drama aspects, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - #180: English language and literature general reading, 1954-1959 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - #182: English teaching, 1952-1959 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - #190-190b: Urban education problems, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - #200: Linguistics, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - #203: Secondary schools teaching, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Heidelberg students, 1953-1957 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Higher Education Title I, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - History (of MAT), 1952-1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Job list, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Newsletter, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Newsletter, 1967-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter and graduate school pamphlets, 1954-1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - North Haven Summer School: science education methods in MAT reading list, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Relations between MAT and related departments: meetings of the committee, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Reports to the president, 1952-1969 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    - Rules and regulations, 1958-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Statistical information, 1953-1970 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
    - Student appraisals, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Student teaching information, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Teacher preparation: preliminary report of the committee, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Teaching preparation: report of the committee, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Undergraduate program, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Yearly files
      - 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 7-9)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5-8)
      - 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - 1968 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
      - End of program, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Primary program, 1968-1976
    - American Institute for Developmental Education (AIDE): conference announcements, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Applicants: staff recruitment, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin school, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Books: requests for complimentary copies, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Council on children, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Certification document (original), Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Child Study Center
      - Advisory Committee: children's literature, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Nursery school, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Staff, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Community resources, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Courses
      - Arts workshop, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - 32a Psychology, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - 49b Psychology, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - 92b Psychology, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - 99b Practice teaching, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 17-18)
      - 101 Psychiatry, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Spring term, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Institute for the Social and Policy Studies: Center for the Study of Education
      - Correspondence, general, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - New Haven schools, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Other models, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Prospects of the program, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Title III: Directors Conference "Frontiers in Education", 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Library
      - Administrative, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Collection development and children's literature collection, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Education policy and social issue collection, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Social science: book lists, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Staff reference and curriculum collection, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Methodology teaching: observation, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Nursery schools, Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Nursery and day care centers, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Public relations, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Recommendations, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Schools
      - Prospect School, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Sacred Heart, the Convent, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Superintendents of School systems interviews (Orange, North Haven, Woodbridge), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Visits in nearby public systems, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - State Department of Education, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Students
      - Applications, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Evaluations, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1-20)
      - Field placement, Undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Grade systems, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - List, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Master teachers, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Meeting minutes, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Reports, Undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Teacher Center New Haven, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Training policies, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Undergraduates, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Vita of faculty for relevant courses, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Yale Daily News, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Summer school, 1960-1970
    - New Haven, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Programs, 1963-1970 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
- Reports of the Yale conferences on the teaching of social studies and English, 1959-1977; Accession 1983-A-057
  - Teaching social studies
    - Reports and speeches, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Reports and speeches, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Reports and speeches, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Reports and speeches, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Negro in America, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Constitution and Consitutionalism, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The City in American History, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The Concept of the Radical in American History, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - History and Education, 1969 Spring (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Teaching about Asia at the Secondary Level, 1969 Fall (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Culture and Society in Early America, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The Revolution and the Bicentennial, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The U.S. Constitution, and Its Development, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The United States Third Century: Issues for the Social Studies, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Teaching english
    - Fifth conference, 1959 April 3-4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Seventh conference, 1961 April 14-15 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Eleventh conference, 1965 April 9-10 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Twelfth conference, 1966 April 7-8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Thirteenth conference, 1967 April 7-8 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Fourteenth conference, 1968 April 5-6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Fifteenth conference, 1969 April 11-12 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Sixteenth conference, 1970 April 10-11 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Records, 1954-1981; Accession 1984-A-035 (Box 1–12)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2016
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Records, 1971-1982; Accession 1984-A-037 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017
- Records, 1973-1984; Accession 1988-A-049 (Box 1–7)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
- Student records, 1977-1988; Accession 1989-A-014 (Box 1–4)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
- Correspondence, 1977-1988; Accession 1990-A-038
  - Fall, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Spring, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Fall, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Spring, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fall, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Spring, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fall, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Spring, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fall, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Spring, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Request for checks, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Request for checks, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Open requistions, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
  - Purchase paid requistions, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Special Students correspondence: Spring, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Special Students correspondence: Fall, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Special Students correspondence: Fall, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Special Students correspondence: Spring, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Special Students correspondence: Fall, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Special Students correspondence: Spring, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Program evaluation, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Trinity, Yale, Wesleyan, Conn, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Fall, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Special Students: Spring, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Special Students: Annual Reports and Grades: Spring, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Special Students: Spring Term, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Division of Special Students: Annual Reports and Grades: Fall, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Special Students: Fall, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Division of Special Students: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Division of Special Students: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Special Students: Fall Term, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Division of Special Students, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bachelor of Liberal Studies: Fall, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - BLS, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - BLS, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - BLS, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Review Evaluation-BLS, 1977-1981
    - Program Development
      - Employees, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Advisory committee, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Financia aid, loans, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Graduate School, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Health Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Private secondary school students, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Transfer students in Yale College, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Wesleyan, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Special students publicity, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Review Evaluation-BLS, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - BLS Booklet, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - BLS Degree Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Responses for Special Students, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Information [Permanently removed to office of origin 4/1990], 1984-1989
  - Telephones, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Xerox Information, Billing Instructions, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Records, 1972-1997; Accession 1998-A-085
  - Auditing, CACUTE, Teacher Placement, and Institute for Urban Education
    - Auditing (Acceptance)-AYA and Relative A-P, 1984-1995 (Box 1)
    - Auditing (Acceptance)-AYA and Relative Q-Z, 1988-1994 (Box 1)
    - Auditors-AYA, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Spring 1984 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Winter 1985 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Fall 1985 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Fall 1986 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Spring 1987 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Fall 1987 (Box 1)
    - Auditing, Spring 1988 (Box 2)
    - Auditing, Fall 1988 (Box 2)
    - Auditing, Spring 1989 (Box 2)
    - Auditing, Fall 1989 (Box 2)
    - CACUTE, 1989-1991 (Box 2)
    - CACUTE, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
    - CACUTE, 1993-1996 (Box 2)
    - Teacher Placement, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
    - Applications Institute for Urban Education, 1993-1997 (Box 2)
  - High School Program
    - Amity High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Amity High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Amity High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Amity Regional High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Amity Regional High, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Amity Regional High, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Amity Senior High, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Branford High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Branford High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Branford High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Career High School, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Daniel Hand High, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - East Haven High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - East Haven High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - East Haven High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - East Haven High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Foran High - Mil., 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Foran High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Guilford High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Guilford High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Guilford High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Guilford High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Guilford High School, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Guilford High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Hamden-New Haven Co-op Ed. Center, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Hamden High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - High School in the Community, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - High School in the Community, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - High School in the Community, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - High School in the Community, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - High School in the Community, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - High School in the Community, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Lee High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Lee High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Career HS, New Haven Coop, HS in the Community., 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Hillhouse High School, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Lee High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Lee High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - New Haven Coop, 1990 (Box 3)
    - New Haven H.S. Program Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - North Branford High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - North Branford High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - North Branford High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - North Branford High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - North Branford High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - North Haven High School, 1990 (Box 3)
    - North Haven Education Career Center (Conte), 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - West Haven High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Wilbur Cross High School, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven HS Program Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Yale New Haven Summer High School, 1990-1993 (Box 3)
  - Special Students Program
    - Special Student BRT's, Fall- Spring, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - Special Students BRT's, Fall- Spring, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
    - Special Student BRT's, Fall- Spring, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
    - Special Student BRT's, Fall- Spring, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
    - Special Student BRT's, Fall- Spring, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
    - Special Student BRT's, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Special Students, Spring, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Special Student BRT's, fall- Spring, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
    - Special Student Inner Office Correspondence., 1972-1977 (Box 4)
    - Special Students Program Correspondence, Spring, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Special Students Correspondence, Fall, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Special Students Correspondence, Spring, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Special Students Correspondence, Fall, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Special Students Correspondence, Spring, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Special Student Correspondence, Fall, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Special Students, Fall, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Special Students Lists, 1988-1990 (Box 4)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Cognition and Teaching Seminar, April, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Dean's Excuses, 1983 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Advisor Reports; Readmission Applications (forms), undated (Box 4)
    - Financial Aid, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Grades, Non- degree, 1981-1988 (Box 4)
    - IUE Rejects, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Make-up Examinations, 1985 (Box 4)
    - RBF Conference, Number 1, March 8-199, #1 (Box 4)
    - RBF Conference, Number 1, March 8-199, #2, 1991 (Box 4)